This is necessary for social media posts?
I can't deal with this. You're going to give me half a pass, you know?
This is your fifth time.
This time? It's my first time.
I'm so tired. I'm so ill of this.
If you don't let me in, I'm going to come in.
Are you the Met Police?
Yes.
This is Phila Madam, how are you?
Not again.
It's you again. You're always with them.
You're under arrest for breach of rail conditions between the 16th of January and the 25th of March.
Okay, I'm going to place you in handcuffs, okay? And then my colleague does.
Why you need the handcuffs?
Okay, so do it properly. Don't do it like last time you hurt her.
My colleague is going to search you, okay?
Oh my God, you do this every single time. I'm so tired of this.
I have to see you every few weeks.
I have to see him every day.
No, seriously, why you do this to my daughter?
You don't have anyone else except Farahmeh?
It's just because she says someone killed children and burned houses and burned tents.
Do you agree with killed children?
You, who come to take care every time. Do you agree with kill children?
No, I'm not. I have a conversation with you.
We're here to do what we've got to do. We need to arrest her.
Can you tell her breach now?
You breach your bail conditions. Your bail conditions are to post things online that are supportive of any terrorist organizations.
So you've posted on, I believe it's on X.
What did she, what did she, what did she post?
Hmm?
What she posted.
Again, I don't need to discuss that with you.
We'll have a phone or some sort of money so you can get back.
No, well you have my phone.
Oh, well you don't need to take your phone if you don't want it.
You, you have it.
No, you have it.
We have your phone.
Yeah, you already have it.
We haven't read it yet, madam.
Would you like to...
This is necessary for social media posts?
So where you take her?
I don't know.
Where you taking her?
Madam, you've asked the same question four times.
Yeah, yeah, I didn't understand.
I didn't understand.
We've called up our controller.
Yeah.
To get some space.
Okay.
We don't know where that space will be yet.
I'm, I'm an ill person.
If you take her to London, how I'm gonna go and find her?
It's, it's, this is what's treating.
It's all what's treating.
Okay, madam.
Yeah, no.
And because we don't want Israel to matter children.
Yeah, yeah.
To matter and under children.
Yeah.
One, two, three, four, five.
Five, police!
Baby, mama.
Why you didn't tell me where you were taking her?
Why?
They won't break us.
I love you, too.
I love you, too, mama.
Be strong, habibti.
We did nothing wrong.
Our government is occupied.
Mandela been arrested.
Same thing.
She was in prison for a while.
Yeah, you've been four, five times, habibti.
Well, arrested, yes.
Alhamdulillah.
Don't leave her without water like last time.
Free Palestine.
Free Palestine, mama.